When I tell y'all that Zionism is running the show and you ignore me, when I tell y'all that
when you support black politicians that are supporting Israel and you get angry with me,
do not then be surprised when you're seeing black journalists in Minneapolis who are giving voice
to the repression being jailed because that is exactly what Zionists were doing and are doing
to journalists in Palestine. And we were telling you, and this is not an I told you so moment,
this is a stop letting it keep happening moment. When you are told and you are shown and it is
demonstrated for you the behavior, respond immediately instead of saying, well, it's over
there. It ain't going to come over here because that's what's happening right now. We got Don
Levin and Georgia Fort arrested for literally just reporting on what is happening, reporting on
repression. It's coming to all of our doorsteps. I'd be on my couch because I'm going to enjoy this
couch as long as I can before they get to my doorstep. So please cut the shit. Understand now
that we are in an entire global version of oppression. It does not just, so please understand
that the Zionist oppression is global. What you've been seeing and hearing about in Palestine is now
happening in Minneapolis. You can't spell Palestine without P-L-S. I actually wonder if either
journalist acknowledged what was going on in Palestine and had any consciousness that it could
happen to them. I'm curious because now all of us know what happened there is happening here.
Not going to happen. It's happening. And just for good measure.